the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from 100 to them IT courses
进行捐赠或查看其他材料从100到他们的IT课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT ided you
麻省理工学院被提供的你
home
家
the
该
in
the new
新
are
有
for
为
over the last several lectures we've dealt with the representation
在过去的几次讲座，我们已经处理了代表
of linear time-invariant systems through convolution
通过卷积线性时不变系统
and just to remind you over basic strategy
而只是提醒你过的基本策略
essentially the idea was to
基本想法是
exploit the notion of when the arity by
利用当元数由概念
decomposing the input into summer basic inputs
分解输入到夏天基本投入
and then using when the arity to tell us that the output can be represented as
然后使用时，元数来告诉我们，输出可以表示为
the corresponding linear combination of the Associated outputs
的相关输出相应的线性组合
so if we have a linear system
因此，如果我们有一个线性系统
either continuous-time and discrete-time for example with continuous time
无论是连续时间和离散时间例如用连续时间
if the input is decomposed as a linear combination
如果输入被分解为一个线性组合
a basic inputs with each of these basic inputs
每个这些基本输入基本输入
generating an Associated output and if the system is linear
产生一个相应的输出，如果该系统是线性的
then the output love the system
那么输出热爱系统
is the same linear combination love The Associated outputs
是一样的线性组合爱相关产出
and the same statement is identical
和相同的语句是相同的
both for continuous-time in discrete-time so
两个连续时间离散时间，以便
the strategy is to decompose the input into these basic inputs
该策略是分解输入到这些基本的输入
and the imports
而进口
were chosen also with some particular
被选为也有一些特殊的
strategy in mind in particular for both continuous-time
策略考虑，特别适用于连续时间
for discrete-time in this representation the
对于离散时间的这种表示的
basic inputs used in the decomposition
在分解中使用的基本输入
are chosen first the ball so that
第一个被选择的球，使
a broad class signals can be represented
一大类的信号可以被表示
interns are these basic inputs and second of all
实习生是这些基本的输入和所有第二
so that the response to these basic inputs
因此，应对这些基本的输入
is in some sense easy to compute now
在某种意义上容易了计算
in the representation which latest
在表示其最新的
to convolution the particular choice that we made
的卷积，我们提出的特定选择
in the discrete-time case for our basic inputs
在离散时间情况下，我们的基本投入
was a decomposition up the input interns
是分解了的输入实习生
or delayed impulses and
或延迟的冲动和
The Associated outputs that that generated
该生成相关产出
were delayed versions of the impulse response
被延迟的脉冲响应的版本
decomposing the input into a linear combination of these
分解输入到它们的线性组合
the output into the corresponding linear combination of these
输出到这些相应的线性组合
then led to the convolution some in
然后导致了卷积一些
the discrete-time case and
离散时间情况和
in the continuous-time case a similar
在连续时间的情况下类似的
kinda decomposition in terms of impulses and Associated representation
还挺分解冲动的条款及相关代表
love the output in terms of the impulse response
爱的脉冲响应的计算的输出
led to the convolution in ago now
导致卷积以前的事了
in this lecture and for number the succeeding lectures
在此讲学和数量后续讲座
will want to turn our attention to a very different
会想将注意力转移到一个非常不同的
said the basic building blocks and
说的基本构建块和
in particular the signals there
特别是那里的信号
will be using as the building blocks for or more general signals
将要使用的积木或更一般的信号
rather than impulses as we've dealt with before
而不是像我们以前处理的冲动
will be in general complex exponentials
将一般复指数
so in a general sense
所以在一般意义上
in the continuous-time case and will be thinking in terms of a decomposition
在连续时间的情况下，将被想到的一个分解的条件
afar signals as a linear combination I'll
远远望去作为信号的线性组合，我将
complex exponentials continuous-time
复指数的连续时间
or in the discrete-time case
或在离散时间情况
complex exponentials where sees the case complex here
复指数在那里看到这里的情况复杂
in discrete-time and s2 K's complex here
在离散时间和s2 K公司的复杂这里
in continuous-time now
在连续时间现在
the basic strategy of course requires
课程的基本战略需要
dead we choose a settlement puts basic building blocks
死了我们选择的和解提出的基本构建块
which have two properties one is that
其中有两个属性之一是
the system response be straightforward to compute were in some sense easy to
系统的响应是直接将计算为在某种意义上容易
compute
计算
and the second is that it be a fairly general said a building blocks
第二个是，它是一个相当普遍的所述一个积木
so that we can build lots of signals I love them
这样我们就可以建立很多的信号，我爱他们
what will find with complex exponentials either continuous-time and discrete-time
什么会发现与复指数无论是连续时间和离散时间
is that they very nicely have those two properties
是他们非常漂亮，有这两个属性
in particular the notion that the
在特定的概念，即
output over linear time-invariant system is easy to compute
输出过线性时不变系统是容易计算
is tied to what's referred to as the eye can function property
绑什么被称为眼可以起到财产
a complex exponentials which will focus on
一个复指数，将重点放在
shortly in a little more detail
不久，在一个稍微详细
and second of all the fact that
和所有的事实，即第二
weekend in fact represent very broad classes have signals as linear
周末其实代表非常广泛的课程有信号，线性
combinations
组合
these will be a topic an issue
这将是一个主题的问题
that will develop in detail over in fact are the next
将详细制定了​​其实就是下一个
set of lectures this lecture and the next set of lectures
一套讲座这个讲座和下一组讲座
now in in doing this although
现在在做这个，虽然
we could in fact begin with our attention focused
我们其实可以开始我们的注意力集中
on in general complex exponentials
在一般复指数
what will choose to do his first focus on the case in which
究竟会选择做他的第一个专注于案件中，
the exponent in the continuous-time cases
在连续时间情况下的指数
purely imaginary as i indicate here
纯属子虚乌有，因为我在这里表示
and in the discrete-time case where
并在离散时间情况下
the magnitude of the complex number Z CK
复数z CK的幅度
is equal to 1 so what that corresponds to in the continuous-time case
等于1有啥对应于在连续时间的情况下
is said building blocks
是说积木
the form you DJ Omega sed Katie
你的DJ欧米茄sed的凯蒂形式
and in the discrete-time case said a building blocks
并在离散时间情况下，所述一个积木
the for eat a DJ Omega KN
在为吃一个DJ欧米茄KN
well we'll see is a representation in these Terms
还有我们会看到，在这些条款的表示
leads to what's for two as for EA
会导致什么两个为EA
analysis and that's what we'll be dealing with over the next several
分析，这就是我们将与处理未来数
lectures
讲座
will then be exploiting this representation actually
然后将实际利用这种表示
through most the course and then toward
通过大多数的过程中，然后向
the end of the course will returned to generalizing
在课程结束时将返回概括
the for a representation to the discussion over plus transforms the
在一个代表性过度加讨论变换
transforms
变换
so for now we want to restrict ourselves to
所以现在我们要限制自己
complex exponentials a particular form in
复指数在一个特定的形式
and in fact also initially to continuous-time
而事实上也是最初到连续时间
signals and systems so let's begin
信号与系统，以便让我们开始
with the continuous-time case the complex exponentials that we want to
与连续时间的情况下，我们希望将复指数
deal with
处理
in and focus first the ball on what I refer to as
并首先集中在球上我指的是
the eigenfunction property love this particular set a building blocks
本征函数属性喜欢这组特定的构建块
we're talking about
我们谈论
basic signals the form either the J Omega some Katy
基本信号的形式无论是歼欧米茄一些凯蒂
and this statement is there
而这种说法是有
for a linear time-invariant system the response to one of these
对于一个线性时不变系统对这些中的一个
is 0 exactly the same form
0是完全相同的形式
just simply multiplied by a complex
只是简单地乘以一个复杂的
factor that complex factor depending on
那复杂的因素取决于因素
what the frequency Omega k is
什么样的频率欧米茄k是
now more or less the justification for this is the proof follows by
现在或多或少的理由，这是证明通过如下
simply looking at the response to a complex exponential
简单地着眼于应对复杂的指数
using the convolution integral so
使用卷积积分，以便
if we put a complex exponential
如果我们把一个复杂的指数
into a linear time-invariant system
成线性时不变系统
with impulse response a gypsy then
用脉冲响应一个吉普赛然后
we can express the response as i've indicated here
我们可以表达的反应，因为我已经在这里表示
we can then recognize that this complex exponential
然后我们能够认识到这个复指数
can be factored into two terms and so
可被分解成两个名词等
we can rewrite this complex exponential
我们可以重写这个复杂的指数
as this product second recognize
作为该产品的第二个认识
that this term can be taken
这个词可以采取
outside the integral over here because of the fact that
因为外面的事实的积分在这里了
it depends only on tea and not on tap now
它只取决于茶叶，而不是现在自来水
and so what we're left with when we tracked this through
还等什么我们留下了，当我们通过跟踪这
is that with a complex exponential input we get
是，与一个复指数的输入，我们得到
an output which is the same complex exponential
这是相同的复指数的输出
namely this factor times
即这个因素倍
this integral and this integral is
这个积分，这积分是
what I referred to above as
我上面提到的
H all omega-6 K
H所有的omega-6 K，
and so in fact we put in a complex exponential
所以实际上我们把一个复杂的指数
we get out a complex exponential love the same frequency
我们得到了一个复杂的爱情指数相同的频率
multiplied by a complex constant and
乘以一个复常数和
that is what's referred to as the eigenfunction property I can function
那是什么被称为本征函数属性，我可以发挥作用
meaning
含义
that and I can function of a system or mathematical expression
这一点，一个系统或数学表达式，我可以发挥作用
is a function which when you put it through the system
是一个函数，当你把它通过系统
comes out looking exactly the same except for a change in amplitude
出来寻找完全相同的，除了振幅的变化
that change in amplitude being the eigen value so
振幅是本征值变化，从而
in fact this function is
实际上这个功能是
the eigenfunction
本征函数
and this bad you
而这个坏你
is the I can bag
是的，我可以包
okay now it's because if the eigenfunction
现在没事了，这是因为，如果本征函数
property that complex exponentials a particularly convenient as building
属性复指数为建设一个特别方便
blocks
块
namely you put it through the system they come out with the same form
即你把它通过他们拿出相同的形式系统
and simply scale the other part to the question related
并简单地扩展其他部分相关的问题
to the strategy that we've been pursuing is
以，我们一直在追求的是战略
to hope that the signals
以希望的信号
can be used as building blocks to represent a
可以用作构建块来表示一个
very broad classes signals through linear combination
很大类信号通过线性组合
and in fact that turns out to be the case with complex exponentials
而事实上该结果是与复指数的情况下
as we worked our way through that
我们通过我们的工作方式
will first consider the case love periodic signals
首先会考虑的情况下爱的周期信号
and what that leads to is a representation a periodic signals
什么是导致是表示一个周期信号
through what's called the forty a series following that
通过什么所谓的40系列以下的
we will turn our attention to non periodic or as I refer to it a periodic
我们将我们的注意力转向非周期或者我把它周期性
signals
信号
and the representation that's developed
而这发展的代表性
interns love linear combinations a complex exponentials
实习生爱的线性组合的复指数
is what's referred to as the 48 transport so
是什么被称为48运输等等
the first thing that we want to deal with our periodic signals
我们要对付我们的周期信号的第一件事
and before you series okay so
和之前系列的这么好吗
what we're talking about then is the continuous-time
我们正在谈论的则是连续时间
for a series and
对于一个系列和
the for a series is a representation for
在一个系列为代表性
periodic continuous-time signals we have
我们有定期的连续时间信号
a signal then which is periodic and
一个信号，然后是周期性的，
were choosing t0 to denote the period
被选择T0表示的期间
so its t0
所以它的T0
then corresponds to the period
然后对应于该期
our periodic signal Omega 0
我们的周期信号欧米茄0
is to party over t0 as
是t0到党对作为
you recall from our discussion love
你从我们的讨论爱情回忆
periodic signals and sinusoids before and that's two pirates 0
前周期信号和正弦信号，这就是两名海盗0
so this is the fundamental frequency now
所以这是基频现
let's examine first the ball complex exponentials
让我们来看看第一个球复指数
and recognize first the ball that
并首先认识到这球
there is a complex exponential that has
有一个复指数，有
exactly the same period and
一模一样的时期，
fundamental frequency as are more general periodic signal
作为更一般的周期信号基波频率
namely the complex exponential you to the jail maker 0t
即复指数你到监狱厂商0吨
where Omega 0 is to Paul II over t0
其中欧米茄0是保禄二世在T0
or equivalent Lee t0 is to pie over Omega 0 now
或同等李T0是馅饼超过欧米茄0现在
that's the complex exponential which has
这是复杂的指数有
t0 as the fundamental period but
T0为基本周期，但
think there are harmonically related complex exponentials
认为有谐波相关复指数
that also have t0 as a period
这也有T0作为一个周期
although in fact their fundamental period shorter
但事实上他们的基本周期较短
so we can also look at complex exponentials
所以我们也可以看看复指数
before either the JK Omega 0t
无论是JK欧米茄0吨前
these likewise are periodic
这些同样是周期性的
with the period love t0
与周期T0的爱
although in fact their fundamental period
但事实上他们的基本周期
is t0 divided by K or equivalently
为T0除以K或等价
to par i divided by their fundamental frequency
以我看齐除以它们的基频
k Omega 0 so as K
K表欧米茄0，因此以K
a richer varies these correspond to
更丰富的这些变化对应于
harmonically related complex exponentials
谐波相关复指数
now with the forty a series
如今随着40系列
says and will justify this kinda bit by bit is the discussion goes I'm
说，将证明这有点儿点点滴滴是讨论去我
what the four-day series says that in fact what for EA
什么样的为期四天的系列说，其实什么EA
said which was essentially the
说这是本质上的
is brilliant insight is that if I have
是辉煌的观点是，如果我有
a very general periodic signal I can represented as a linear combination of
非常一般的周期信号能表示为的线性组合
these harmonically related
这些谐波相关
complex exponentials so
复指数的声音
that representation is what i've indicated here
这代表的是什么，我在这里表示
and this summation is
这是求和
what will be referred to as
什么将被称为
the for EA
在对EA
series
系列
and as we proceed with the discussion there are two issues
当我们着手讨论有两个问题
couldn't that will develop one is assuming
不能，将开发一种是假设
that our periodic signal can be represented this way
我们的周期信号可以表示这样
how do we determine the for a series coefficients
我们如何确定的一系列系数
as they refer to a suitcase that's one question
因为它们都指向一个手提箱这是一个问题
and the second question will be
而第二个问题将是
how broad a class of signals in fact can be represented that
如何广泛的一类，事实上信号可以表示该
this way and bats another question their
这种方式和蝙蝠又质疑自己
will deal with separately
将分别处理
now just focusing on this representation
现在只需专注于这种表示
for a minute this representation
一分钟，这表示
love the four EA series which
爱的四个EA系列里面
I repeated again
我又重复了一遍
here
这里
is what's referred to as the complex
是什么被称为复
exponential form love for EA series
对EA系列指数形式的爱
and it's important to note incidently
而且要注意顺便说一句很重要
day this summation involves frequencies k Omega 0
一天，这个总和涉及频率K表欧米茄0
their are both positive and negative
他们是正面和负面的
in other words this index K runs over
换句话说，这个指数的日K运行于
limits that include both negative values and positive ads
限制，包括消极的价值观和积极的广告
now that complex exponential form is one
现在，复杂的指数形式之一
representation for before you a series
对于之前的一系列代表性
and in fact it's the one that we will be principally
而事实上它是一个我们将主要
relying on in this course there is another representation that
在这个过程中依靠有另一种表示形式
perhaps you come across previously
也许你以前碰到过
and that in a variety of other contacts is
而且在其他各种接触是
is typically used which is called the trigonometric form
通常用于这就是所谓的三角形状
the forty a series without really tracking through the algebra
四十一系列不通过代数真的跟踪
essentially we can get to the trigonometric for
基本上我们可以得到的三角为
from the complex exponential form by
从由复指数形式
recognizing that if we express the complex coefficients
认识到，如果我们表示复系数
in polar for or in rectangular for
在极地或矩形的
and expand the complex exponential
并扩大复指数
term out in terms of cosine plus J sign
长期在余弦方面加Ĵ的标志
using just simply Oilers relation then
只用简单的油工关系，然后
in we will end up with the representation
在我们最终会与代表
for the periodic signal
为周期性信号
were a re expression love the for a series
被重新表达爱的系列
expression that we had previously either in the form that I indicate here
我们曾经无论是在我这里显示的形式表达
we're now the periodic signal is expressed
我们现在的周期信号表示
in terms of a summation love cosines
在求和爱余弦条款
with appropriate ample to in phase
适当充足的在相
or another acquittal or triggered a metric for
或另一无罪或引发度量
involves rearranging this
涉及重新安排这
in terms or a combination
在条款或组合
of cosines and signs now
余弦和现在的迹象
in this representation the frequencies of the sinusoids
在此表示的正弦波的频率
very only over positive frequencies
只有极了正频率
and typically one thinks
和一般人认为
of periodic signals is having positive frequencies associated with them
周期信号是有与它们相关联正频率
however let's look back
然而，让我们回顾一下
at the complex exponential form
在复指数形式
for the forty a series at the top of the board
第四十一个系列在电路板的顶层
and in that representation when we use this representation
并在这代表当我们使用这种表示方法
will find it convenient to refer to both
将是方便的同时指
positive frequencies and negative frequencies so
正频率和负频率等等
the representation that we will most typically be using is the complex
我们将最通常使用的表示为复
exponential form
指数形式
and in that form what will find as we think it decomposing a periodic signal
并以这种形式究竟会发现，因为我们认为它分解周期信号
in to its compliments
在它的赞美
at different frequencies it will involve both positive frequencies
在不同的频率会同时涉及正频率
negative frequencies
负频率
okay now we have the
现在没事了，我们有
for EA series representation as i've indicated here
对EA系列的代表性，因为我已经在这里表示
again so far I sidestepped the issue as
再次到目前为止，我回避了这个问题，因为
to whether this in fact represents all the signals that we'd like to represent
这是否实际上代表了所有我们想代表信号
let's first address the issue
让我们先来解决这个问题
love how we determine these coefficients
爱我们如何确定这些系数
Acer K assuming that in fact this representation is Val
宏碁ķ假设，其实这种表示是Val
and again all kinda move through the algebra
并再次全部还挺移动通过代数
fairly quickly its a the outbreak steps the ones that
很快它的一个爆发步骤是那些
you can pursue more leisurely just the kinda
你可以只是有点追求更悠闲
verify them in step through them but
验证它们在通过他们的一步，但
essentially the algebra develops I did the recognition
本质上是代数的发展我也承认
that if we integrate a complex exponential
如果我们整合一个复杂的指数
over one period t0
在一个周期T0
and I mean by this notation that this is an integral
我通过这种表示法意味着这是一个整体
over a period where I don't particularly care
过了一段，我并不特别关心
where the period starts and where the period stops in other words
其中期开始和其中换言之期间停止
exactly what period I picked that this integral
我挑到底是什么时期，这个积分
is equal to t0 when M is equal to 0
等于T0当M等于0时
and it's equal to 0 if am is not equal to 0
而且它等于0，如果点是不等于0的
that follow simply from the fact that if we substitute in
从事实遵循简单地说，如果我们在替换
for using Oilers relations so that we have the integral to cosign
使用油工关系，使我们有不可或缺的余弦
was J times assign if M
是的J倍指派如果M
is not equal to 0 than
是不等于0的比
of these integrals over a period are
这些积分在一段是
0 the integral over sign it a periodic have a sinus or a cosigner sign
0积分超过它标志一个周期有一个鼻窦或联署标志
over an integral number periods is zero whereas
在整数周期是零，而
if M is equal to 0 this in a crawl
如果M等于0这在抓取
will be equal to 20 the integral the cosine
将等于20的积分余弦
and the integral on the sign is equal to
并且在该标志的积分是相等
okay well the next step
还好以及下一步
in developing the expression for the coefficients a Sat K
在发展表达式系数a周六Ķ
is to refer back to
是指回
before a series expression which was that except he
这是一系列的表达式之前，除了他
is equal to the sum with basic K either the JK Omega 0t
等于与基本ķ任JK欧米茄0吨总和
if we multiply both sides that by either minus
如果我们乘双方的任何一方负
jaan Omega 0t and
朱展欧米茄0吨和
integrate that over a period
整合了一段
both sides of the equation integrated over a period
在等式两边集成在一段
so these two equations are equal and then
所以这两个方程是相等的，然后
in essence interchange the summation and the integration
在本质上交换求和及积分
so that this pardon the expression cons outside the psalm
所以，这个赦免诗篇外表达的利弊
and then we combine these two complex exponentials together
然后我们结合这两种复指数一起
where we come out is
我们走出来的
the expression that i've indicated here in
我已经在这里表示在表达式
and then essentially what happens at this point algebraically
然后基本上什么在这一点上发生代数
is that we use the result that we just developed
是我们使用，我们刚刚开发的结果
to evaluate this cynical so
评估这种愤世嫉俗所以
multiplying both sides the forty a series in and doing the integration
乘双方的40系列中，做整合
leads us after the appropriate manipulation
相应的操作后，使我们
to the expression that
该表达式
I have up here and
我在这里和
this is equal to
这等于
this integral is equal to t0
这个积分等于T0
if K is equal to an
如果K等于一个
corresponding 20 up here and 80
相应的20在这里和80
otherwise which is what we have demonstrated or are you previously
否则这就是我们已经证明，或者是你以前
and the upshot of all that then is that
和所有的结果则是，
the right hand side if this expression disappears
右手侧，如果该表达式中消失
except for the term when K is equal to n
除了当K等于n的术语
and so finally we have what I indicate here
所以最后我们有什么我在此说明
taking t0 and moving it over to the other side of the equation
服用t0和移动它交给等式的另一边
we then that then tells us
我们那么然后告诉我们
how we determine the forty a series coefficients
我们如何判断40一个级数的系数
a7 Auris K so
A7耳Ķ所以
that in effect and is the
在效果，并且是
what we refer to as the analysis equation the equation that begins with
我们所说的分析方程开头的方程
excessive to me
过度的给我
and tells us how to get the for a series coefficients
并告诉我们如何获得的一系列系数
what are referred to as
什么被称为
the 48 series synthesis equation
48系列合成公式
is the equation that tells us
就是告诉我们的方程式
how to build exit see outta love
如何建立退​​出看见失控的爱情
these complex exponentials so we have the synthesis equation
这些复杂的指数函数，所以我们有合成公式
which is the one that we started from we have
这是我们从我们开始了一个
the analysis equation which is the equation
分析方程，为方程
that we just developed
我们刚刚开发
okay so we in effect have
好了，所以我们实际上有
going through the issue love assuming there for a series representation
经历了爱情的问题假设有一个系列的代表性
is in fact valid how we get
其实有效的，我们怎么弄
the coefficients we want to address
我们要解决的系数
somewhat the question love how broad a classic signals that we're talking
有些问题爱怎么广义经典的信号，我们正在谈论
are we talking about and what's in fact amazing
我们谈论的是，什么是事实上惊人
and was for EA's amazing insight
并为EA的惊人的洞察力
was that it's a very broad class say but
是，它是一个非常广泛的一类，但说
let's first look at just some examples
让我们先来看看一些例子
in which we take a signal assume that it has the Fourier series representation
在此我们需要一个信号假设它有傅立叶级数表示
and see what the for a series coefficients look like so
看看是什么为一系列系数看起来像这样
will begin with what I refer to as
将开始与我所说的
an antisymmetric periodic square wave periodic of course because we're talking
当然反对称周期的方波周期，因为我们正在谈论
about periodic signals
关于周期信号
square wave referring to its shape and
方波指的是其形状和
antisymmetric referring to the fact that it is an odd
反对称指这样的事实，它是一个奇
time function in other words it is antisymmetric
换句话说，时间函数是反对称的
about the origin now
关于现在的起源
the expression for the for a series coefficients
为表达为一系列系数
tells us that we determine a sieve K
告诉我们，我们判断一个筛子Ķ
by taking one over 20 times the integral over a period
通过采取不可分割的单超过20倍过一段
affects 50 either minus JK Omega 0t
影响50或者减去JK欧米茄0吨
DT the most convenient thing in this case
DT在这种情况下，最方便的事
is to choose a period which
是选择的期间，
let's say goes from minus 20 over to the plus 20 over to
让我们说去从零下20多到20加过来
so here except he is -1 here
所以这里除了他是这里-1
expertise plus one and so
专业知识加1等
I've expressed the for a series called efficiency as
我已经表达了对一系列被称为效率
this integral that's from minus 20 over
这个积分这是从零下20多
and then and it said that is the
然后，它说，是
positive part of the cycle and so we have
周期的积极组成部分，所以我们有
these two integrals now I don't want to
这两个积分现在我不想
tracked through the details both the algebra again I
通过细节都再次代数跟踪我
I guess I've decided that that's much more fun for you do on your own
我想我已经决定，这是更有趣为你做你自己
but the way it comes out when you go through it
但它出来时，你通过它的方式
is the expression that I finally indicate after
为表达我后，终于显示
suggesting that there are a few more steps to follow
提示有几个步骤如下
and what develops is that
什么发展是
those two integrals together for K
这两个积分一起于K
not equal to 0 come out to this expression
不等于0出来这个表达
and that expression is not valid for k equal to 0
而且表达式无效对于k等于0
per kg equal to 0 we can go back to
每公斤等于0，我们可以回去
the basic expression for the forty a series
基本表达式为40系列
which is one over t0 the integral over a period
这是一个比T0的积分在一段
exit see in the minus JK Omega 0 /td TD
在零下JK欧米茄0 / TD TD出口看
for cake 10 of course this term
当然对于蛋糕10这个术语
just simply becomes one and
只是简单地变成一个，
so the zeroth coefficient is one over 20 times the integral
所以零系数是不可分割的单超过20倍
X 50 over a period now
X 50过了一段现在
going back to the original function
回到原来的功能
that we have what we're saying then is that
我们有我们在说什么，然后是
0th coefficient is one over 20 times the integral over
第0系数是超过20倍的积分超过
one period which is in effect the average value
1期是有效的平均值
and it straight forward to verify the for this case that average value
它直截了当地验证了这种情况的平均值
is equal to 0 okay
等于0好
now let's look at
现在让我们来看看
these for a series coefficients on a bar graph
这些对于一个条形图一系列系数
and i've indicated that here the
我已经指出，这里的
expression for the for a series coefficients we just developed and
为为一系列系数，我们刚刚开发与表达
a involves its
一个涉及其
0 for cake 0 it's a factor this form
0蛋糕0这是一个因素这种形式
for canine equal to 0 plotted on a bar graph
犬等于0上绘制条形图
then we see values like this 0
然后，我们看到这样的0值
at cake 0 and and associated values
在蛋糕0和关联的值
and their number things to focus on
其数量的东西集中在
when you look at this
当你看这个
one is the fact that the forty a series coefficients for this example
1是一个事实，即40对本例的一系列系数
are surely imaginary
肯定是虚构的
a second is that the Fourier series coefficients for this example
第二个是，在这个例子中的傅里叶级数的系数
are odd sequence in other words if you look at this sequence which you see
在换句话说奇数序列，如果你看一下这个序列，你看
are these values for negative K
这些值的阴K
flipped over so there their imaginary
翻转过来，让他们有虚
and odd and
和奇数和
what that results in when
是什么导致了当
you look at the
你看看
the triggered a metric form the 4e a series
触发度量形式的4E系列
is that in fact those conditions if you put the terms altogether
是，事实上，如果这些条件你把干脆条款
lead you to a trigger a metric representation
带你到一个触发度量表示
which involves only sign terms
其中只涉及迹象条款
in other words no co-signed turns let me just draw your attention to the fact
换句话说，没有共同签署轮流让我提请你注意这样的事实：
that
那
since a suitcase the acer case or imaginary
因为一个手提箱宏基情况或虚
this jay takes care that fact so that these coefficients
这杰伊需要照顾，事实上使这些系数
are in fact real so what this says
其实真正的有啥此说
is that for the antisymmetric square wave the
是，对于反对称方波的
it in effect the forty a series is a sign series
它实际上四系列是一个标志系列
the antisymmetric square wave is an odd function
反对称方波是奇函数
sinusoids are not are odd functions and so this is all kinda reasonable that
血窦不能是奇函数，所以这是所有还挺合理的
we're building
我们正在构建
odd function ido odd functions
奇函数IDO奇函数
as an additional aside which a I won't
作为一个额外拨出其中一个我不会
exploit or refer to any further here
利用或参考任何进一步这里
but just draw your attention to is that another aspect
但只是提请您注意的是，另一个方面
love this periodic square wave the particular one that we chose
喜欢这个周期性方波的特定的一个，我们选择了
is dead it is what's referred to as a
是死是什么被称为
on harmonic function in other words
上，换句话说谐函数
for even values if K
即使值在K
before a series coefficients 30 their only 90
一系列系数30的只有90才
for iPad use K
为iPad利用类型K
okay now let's look at another example another example
好吧，现在让我们来看另一个例子另一个例子
is the symmetric periodic square wave
是对称周期的方波
and this is in fact example
这实际上是在例如
4.5 worked out in more detail in the tax then
4.5制定了详细的税收再
I won't bother to work work this out in detail here
我不想在这里工作的工作这一点详细
except to draw your attention to several
除了提请你注意的几个
points here is the symmetric periodic square wave
点这里是对称周期的方波
and what I mean by symmetric
和我说的对称
is that it's an even time function
是，它是一个更时间功能
now just kinda extrapolating your intuition
现在只是有点推断你的直觉
what we you should expect is that if if it's a
我们应该期待什么，如果，如​​果它是一个
only even time function it should be built up
即使只有一次函数应该建立
or buildable if it's built up a little %ah to only
或可建，如果它建立了一点点％啊，只
even sinusoids and in fact
甚至血窦和实际上
that's the case so if we look at
是这样的话，所以如果我们看
the four-day series coefficients for this
这个为期四天的一系列系数
the zeroth coefficient again as the average value
再次第零系数的平均值
which in this case is a half here I've plotted
在这种情况下是半这里我绘制
hi times the for a series coefficients so
喜倍的一系列系数，从而
0 thank you as pie over to
0感谢你的馅饼交给
the coefficients are now and even sequence
该系数是现在乃至序列
and in in other words symmetric
和在换言之对称
about cake 0 and the consequences that
关于蛋糕0和后果
is that when you take these coefficients
是，当你把这些系数
and put together the equivalent triggered a metric form
并放在一起，相当于触发一个度量形式
the triggered a metric for involves
触发一个度量涉及
only cosines and no
只有余弦和无
sign turns now
现在标记变为
you'll see this in and other examples not that will do in the lecture but
你会看到这一点和其他的例子不就是会做演讲，但
examples in the text in the video manual if in fact
在视频说明书文本的例子，如果实际上
the square way was neither symmetric or antisymmetric
广场路既不是对称或反对称
then the trigonometric form would involve both
那么三角函数形式将涉及两个
sines and cosines and
正弦和余弦和
that is of course the more general case
这当然是更一般的情况
furthermore in the two examples are shown here
此外在这两个例子都在这里显示
we we in both cases
我们大家在这两种情况下
the signal is odd harmonic
该信号是奇次谐波
in other words for even bad news K
换句话说，即使坏新闻K
the coefficients are equal to 0 although I won't justify that here that's a
该系数等于0，虽然我不会辩解，在这里，这是一个
consequence that the fact that
结果是一个事实，即
this symmetry is exactly about half a period
这种对称性正是大约半期
and if you made the on time with a square wave
如果你有一个方波所做的时间
different in relation to the of time then that property would also
有关的时间不同，那么该属性也
disappear
消失
now
现在
what's kind amazing actually in
有什么样的惊人实际上是在
is that if we take a square wave like
是，如果我们把一个方波像
I have here or as I had in the antisymmetric case
我这里还是因为我曾在反对称情况
the implication is that I can bill
其含义是，我可以账单
that square wave by adding up
该方波通过加
on of signs were cosines and
对标志是余弦和
it really seems kinda amazing because the square wave after all
它似乎真的有点惊人的，因为方波毕竟
is a very discontinuous functions
是一个非常不连续的函数
sinusoids are very continuous and it seems puzzling that in fact
血窦非常连续，似乎令人费解，其实
you can do that well let's look in a little bit of detail
你可以做的那么好，让我们来看看详细的一点点
how the sinusoidal
如何正弦
turns and up to
打开和高达
build a square wave and to do that
建设方波，要做到这一点
let's first define what I refer to
让我们先来定义什么我指的是
as a partial song so
作为一个部分的歌曲等等
here we have the expression
在这里，我们有表达
which is the synthesis
它是合成
equation telling us how accept T could be represented
公式告诉我们如何接受Ŧ可以表示
as complex exponentials if it can be and
如果为复指数它可以和
let's consider just a finite number of turns in this song
让我们考虑的圈在这首歌只是数量有限
and so X 7ft of course as n goes to infinity
和则X当然，随着n的7英尺趋于无穷
approaches the infinite sum that we're talking about and although we could do
方法，我们正在谈论的无限求和，虽然我们可以做
this more generally let's not let's focus on the symmetric square wave case
这更普遍，我们不要让我们专注于对称方波的情况下
where because it the symmetry of these coefficients namely that a suitcase
在那里，因为它这些系数的对称性即一个手提箱
equal to minus
等于负
is equal to a serb minus K we can rewrite
等于一个塞族零下•我们可以重写
these turns as cosine turns and so this partial some
这些匝数为余弦转弯，所以这部分的一些
can be express the way arm expressing it here
可以表达手臂的方式在这里表达
well let's look at
也让我们来看看
a few the Stearns on the graph I have
几个贝尔斯登在图形上我有
first the ball exit tea which is our
第一球出口茶叶这是我们的
original square wave
原来的方波
the turn that I indicate here
该轮到我在此说明
is the factor over half which
超过一半的因子，它
is this term
就是这个词
with any calls one that would correspond to anyone co-signed term
与任何调用一个会符合任何人共同签署期限
to that and so the sole those two would be yes
到这一点，所以唯一的两个人会是肯定的
which looks a little close to the square wave but
这看起来有点接近方波，但
certainly not very close to it at all and in fact
当然不是非常接近它在所有与实际上
in its somewhat hard to imagine without
在某种程度上很难想象没有
seeing the terms build-up how in fact by adding more and more turns we can
眼看条款积聚如何，其实通过添加更多和更多的匝数，我们可以
generate something
生成的东西
that is essentially flat except at the discontinuities
这基本上是平的，除了在不连续
so let's look at this example and what I'd like to show
所以让我们来看看这个例子，我想展示
is this example but now as we add many
就是这个例子，但现在，我们增加了许多
more turns to it and let's see in fact
更多转向它，让我们事实上看到
how these individual turns add up
如何将这些各匝加起来
to build up the square way so
建立起来的方方式，使
this is the square wave that we want to build up
这是我们要建立的方波
through the forty a series is this some of sinusoids
经过四十一个系列是一些血窦
and the term for cake 0 will be a constant which represents the DC value
和术语蛋糕0将代表直流电值恒定
with this
与此
and so in the partial sum as we develop it
所以在我们开发它的部分和
the first thing they will show is just the term for cable 0
他们将显示的第一件事就是术语电缆0
now for cables one we would add to that
现在的电缆之一，我们将添加到该
one sinusoidal term and
一个正弦项和
so some love the term for cake was one cake was 0
所以一些爱术语蛋糕1蛋糕是0
is represented here now
这里指现时
when we go to K calls to because of the fact that this is an odd harmonic
我们去的时候，因为一个事实，即这是一个奇次谐波来调用K到
function
功能
in fact the term for cake was it was too
其实这个词的蛋糕是它太
will be will have zero amplitude and so this won't change
将将具有零幅度，所以这不会改变
here we show the
在这里，我们将展示
for a series would cake was to and there's no change
对于一系列将蛋糕并没有变化
and then we will go to cable 23
然后我们将去23线
and
和
and we will be adding then one additional sinusoidal term here's cake
我们将增加那么这里一个额外的正弦项的蛋糕
was three
是三
when we go to cable 24 again there won't be any change
当我们去到电缆24再次将不会有任何改变
but their will be another term that's
但他们的将是另一个术语，它是
added at cake was five here and cable 6
在蛋糕中加入五岁这里和电缆6
again because it's odd harmonic no change and finally cable 7
又因为它的奇次谐波没有改变，最后电缆7
is shown here okay and we can begin to see that
这里显示没关系，我们可以开始看到
this starts to look somewhat like the square wave but
这开始看起来有点像方波，但
now to really emphasize how this builds up let's
现在要真正强调的是如何建立起来让我们
more rapidly and Ed many more terms and in fact
更迅速和Ed有更多的方面和实际上
increase the number of turns up to about a hundred recognizing
增加圈数高达约一百承认
that the shape will only change on the inclusion
该形状将仅改变对夹杂物
all the odd number terms not the even-numbered turns because it's an odd
所有奇数条款不是偶数转弯，因为它是一个奇怪的
harmonic function so now we're
调和函数所以现在我们
increasing and we're building up toward
增加，我们正在建立对
k equal to 100 200 turns an
ķ等于100 200变为一个
notice that it is the higher
注意，它是较高的
order turns dead tend to build up
为了变成死倾向于建立
the discontinuity corresponding to the notion
对应于所述概念的不连续性
there'd the discontinuities or sharp edges in a signal
那里倒是在一个信号中的不连续性或尖锐的边缘
in fact are represented through the higher
实际上是通过较高的代表
frequencies in the forty a series and here we have
在40系列，在这里我们有频率
a not too unreasonable approximation
一个不太合理的近似
to the original square wave there is the artifact of the ripples at the
原来的方波存在的涟漪在神器
discontinuity and in fact
不连续性和实际上
though that rippling behavior at the discontinuities
虽然在不连续的行为荡漾
is referred to as the Gibbs phenomenon
被称为吉布斯现象
and it's an inherent part love the forty a series representation at
和它的一个固有部分爱40在一系列的代表性
discontinuities
不连续
now to emphasize this
现在强调这
let's decrease the number of turns back down
让我们来减小匝数回​​落
and we will carry this down
我们会进行下来
to k equal to 1 again
于k等于1再次
to emphasizes how the sinusoids are building up
要强调的是如何血窦正在建立
the square wave here we are back at Cape cools
方波在这里我们又回到海角冷却
1 and then finally we
1，然后最后我们
will and back in the sinusoids that we took out
将和回到我们拿出血窦
and let's build this back up to 100 turns
并让我们建立这个备份到100圈
showing the approximation dead
显示近似死
we generated with a hundred turns to the square way
我们有一百产生轮流到广场路
okay so so what you saw is that
好了，所以你看到的是，
in fact we got awfully close to a square wave
其实我们得到了非常接近方波
and the other thing think that was kind of interesting about it is that went
和其他的事情认为是一种有趣的关于它是去
along
沿
was the fact that with the low frequencies
的事实是，与低频
what we were tending to bill was the general behavior
什么我们倾向于法案是一般的行为
and as the higher frequencies came in
和更高的频率来在
that tended to contribute the discontinuities
这往往做出贡献的不连续性
work contribute to the discontinuity and
工作做出贡献的不连续性和
in fact something their will
其实一些自己的意志
standout more and more as we go through our discussion
杰出的事物越来越多，因为我们通过我们的讨论
love for a series of 48 transforms is
对于一系列48变换为爱
that general statement that its the low-frequency
该一般性发言，它的低频
terms bat represent
条款蝙蝠代表
the broad time behavior and
广阔的时间和行为
its the high-frequency terms that are used to build up
其被用于建立高频条款
the sharp transitions in the time domain
急剧转变中的时域
okay now we need to get a little more precise
还好现在我们需要得到更确切的一点
about the question of how in fact
有关如何在事实问题
the 48 series
48系列
or when before you a series represents
或者当你前一个系列代表
the functions that we're talking about and in what sense they represent them
我们正在谈论的和在什么意义上，他们代表他们的功能
in and so if we look
在所以如果我们看
again at the synthesis
再次在合成
ok wage in were really wanna ask
在确定工资真的想问问
is if we add up enough for these terms
就是如果我们添加了足够的这些条款
in what sense does this some represent
在何种意义上这方面的一些代表
this time function well
这个时间的功能以及
let's again use the notion love are partial some
让我们再次使用这个概念的爱都是一些偏
so we have the partial song down here
所以我们有部分歌曲到这里
in and we can think love the difference between
在我们能想到爱的区别
this partial some and the
这部分的一些和
original time function as
原来时间功能
the ever and I've defined the error here
不断和我在这里定义的错误
and what we would like to know is does this error
而我们想知道的是这个错误
decrease as we aired more and more turns
减少，因为我们播出越来越多的匝数
and in fact in what sense if the air does decrease in what sense
而事实上在何种意义上，如果空调确实减少在何种意义
there's a decrease now in detail
有一个减少现在详细
this is a fairly complicated an elaborate topic I don't mean to make
这是一个相当复杂的一个精心制作的主题我的意思不是让
that sound frightening
听起来可怕
its mainly a statement that I don't want to explore it and a lot of detail
其主要是我不想去探索它，很多细节的陈述
but it relates to what is referred to
但它涉及到什么被称为
as the issue a convergence the forty a series
作为这一问题的收敛四十一系列
and the convergence the 48 series
和收敛的48系列
the the bottom line on at the kinda and statement
就在有点和声明底线
can be made in several ways one statement
可以用几种方式之一语句来
related to convergence the for a series is the following if
以收敛为一个系列的以下相关，如果
I have a time function which
我有一个时间函数，
is what is referred to as square integrable namely
是什么被称为平方可积即
its integral over a period is finite then
它的积分在一个周期是有限的，然后
what you can show kinda amazingly
你能告诉是什么样的惊人
is that the energy E in
的是，在能量E
that error in other words the energy in the difference between the original
换句话说，能量在原来的区别是错误
function
功能
and the partial some the energy and that
和局部的一些能量，并且
goes to zero as n goes to infinity
趋近于零当n趋于无穷
a somewhat tighter condition is a condition referred to as it the racially
一个有点严格条件是指它在种族条件
conditions which says that
条件说
if the time function
如果时间功能
is absolutely integral not square honorable but absolutely integral
绝对是不可或缺的不是正方形的光荣，但绝对是不可或缺的
and I've kinda hedge the issue by just simply referred to accept T as being
我已经被刚刚简称接受T作为是有点冲的问题
well behaved
很乖
then the statement is dead the error in fact goes to zero
那么该语句是死的，其实误差趋于零
as and increases except at the discontinuities
如，除了在不连续性和增加
and what well-behaved means in that statement
在该声明中，什么乖巧的手段
is that as discussed in the book there are a finite number
是因为在本书中讨论有数量有限
maxima and minima in any period and a finite number finite discontinuities
最大值和最小值在任何时期和有限数量有限的不连续性
which is essentially
这实质上是
always the case so under square in Accra bility
总是那么下广场阿克拉bility的情况下
what we have is the statement not that the partial sum goes to the right value
我们所拥有的是语句不是部分和去正确的价值
at every point
在每一点上
but that the energy in the air goes to zero
但是，在空气中的能量变为零
under the jewish way conditions it says that in fact the signal goes to the
犹太人的方式条件下，它说，事实上，信号变到
right back to you
马上回你
at every time instant except
除了在每一次瞬间
at the discontinuities so
在这样的不连续性
going back to the square wave
回到方波
the square wave satisfies either one of those conditions and so
方波满足任一条件者等
what the consequences is that with the square wave
其后果是什么，与方波
if we looked at the error then in fact
如果我们看了看错误，那么实际上
what we would find is that the energy
我们所发现的是，能
in the error would go to zero as we at
在错误会去到零，因为我们在
more and more turns in the partial some and in fact
在一些局部和实际上越来越多匝
if says the square wave also satisfies the dish les conditions
如果说，方波也满足了菜莱条件
the actual value with the air the difference between
与空气之间的差的实际值
the partial some and the true value will will
局部和一些真正的价值将将
actually go to zero that difference will go to zero
实际上变为零的差异将变为零
except at the discontinuities and
除了上面的不连续性和
that in fact is kinda evident as
那其实是有点明显的，因为
we watch the function build-up
我们看功能集结
by adding up these terms and so in fact
在事实上增加了这些条款等
let's go back and see again
让我们回去再看看
the development the partial sons
发展中的部分子
in relation to the original time function let's observe
相对于原有的计时功能，让我们观察
this time again basically what we saw before which is that it builds up
此时再次基本上是我们以前看见的是，它建立了
to the right answer and furthermore what will plot this time also as a function
正确的答案，此外什么将绘制这个时候也作为一个函数
of time
时间
is the energy in the air and what we'll see is that the energy in the air
是在空气中的能量，以及我们将看到的是，在空气中的能量
will be tending toward zero as the number
将朝向零的数目来趋向
turns increases so
原来如此增加
once again we have the square wave and
再次，我们拥有方波和
we want to again show the buildup of the
我们要再次显示的积聚
forty a series this time showing also
40系列这一次还展示
how the energy in the air decreases as we had more and more turns
如何在空气中的能量减小，因为我们有越来越多匝
well once again will begin
以及再次将开始
with cake was 0 corresponding to the constant term
与蛋糕被相应的常数项0
and was shown on the bottom trace is
并显示在底部的痕迹是
the energy in the air between those two and
这两个和之间的能量在空气中
will then and the term for cables 1
之后会和术语电缆1
to the DC term and will see that the energy will decrease
到DC任期，并看到能量将减少
when we do that here we have then the summer
当我们这样做，在这里我们有那么夏天
cake 10 cables 1 now
蛋糕10线1现在
with cables to the energy won't decrease
用电缆将能量不会减少
any further because it's an odd harmonic function
任何进一步的，因为它是一个奇次谐波功能
that's what we've just added in when we add in the term for cables 3
这就是我们刚刚添加的，当我们添加的期限为3电缆
again will see the energy in the air decrease
再次将看到的能量在空中减少
as reflected in the bottom curve
这反映在底部曲线
so there we are at cables 3 when
所以我们在电缆3时
we go to cable 24 there again is no change in the air
我们去的电缆24再次出现在空气中无变化
at cables 5 again the air decreases
在电缆5再次降低空气
k equal to 6% know there will be no change again
ķ等于6％知道有将再次没有变化
an 8k course 7 the energy decreases
一个8K当然7的能量减少
and now let's show the how the air decreases by building up the number
现在，让我们通过建立数字显示的是如何减少空气
turns much more rapidly already the air has gotten somewhat small on the scale
原来快得多已经在空气已经变得有些小的规模
in which were showing it so let's expand out
其中显示了它让我们拓展出
the ever scale the vertical axis
不断扩展，垂直轴
displaying the energy in the error so that we could watch
显示在错误的能量，使我们可以看
how the energy decreases as
如何能随着
we had more and more terms so here we have
我们有越来越多的方面所以在这里我们有
the vertical scale expanded and
垂直刻度扩大，
now what we'll do is increase
现在我们要做的就是增加
the number of turns in the forty a series and watch the energy in the air
圈中的40系列的数目和观看的能量在空气中
at decreasing
在减少
always decreasing of course on the inclusion
总是递减的过程中就列入
love the odd number turns and
爱奇绕组匝数
not on the inclusion of the even-numbered turns because the fact
不包含偶数匝，因为事实
that it's an odd harmonic function now the energy in the air
这是一个奇怪的调和函数现在的能量在空中
asymptotically will approach 0 although
渐近将接近0，虽然
point by point the forty a series will never be equal to the square wave
逐点的40系列永远不会等于方波
it will at every instant of time
它会在每个时间瞬间
except at the discontinuities where there will always be
除了在不连续的地方，总是会有
some ripple corresponding to
对应于一定的纹波
what's referred to as the Gibbs phenomenon
什么是被称为吉布斯现象
okay well so what we've seen in is
好舒服，所以我们所看到的是
a and a quick look at the Fourier series
一个又一个快速浏览一下傅里叶级数
representation love periodic signals
代表爱情的周期信号
we more broadly
我们更广泛地
wanna have a more general representation
希望有一个更一般的表示
love oath signals in terms of complex exponentials and so our next step
在复指数方面，所以爱的誓言信号，我们的下一个步骤
will be to move toward a representation
将走向一个代表性
I'll not periodic or a periodic signals
我不会定期或周期信号
now the details if this I leave for the next lecture
现在的细节，如果这让我在接下来的演讲
the only thought that I want introduced at this point
我在这一点上希望推出的唯一的想法
is the basic strategy you which
是基本策略你的
is somewhat amazing and kinda interesting to reflect on
是有点惊人的，还挺有趣的反思
in the interim the basic strategy
在此期间的基本策略
with in a periodic signal is
在一个周期信号是
to think love representing
想表示爱
this a periodic signal as a linear combination of complex exponentials
本周期信号作为复指数的线性组合
by this simple trick all
通过这个简单的技巧都
periodically replicating this signal
定期复制此信号
generating a periodic signal
生成的周期信号
using a Fourier series representation
用傅立叶级数表示
for that periodic signal and then
对于周期性的信号，然后
simply letting the period go to infinity
只是让期间去到无穷大
as the period goes to infinity that periodic signal becomes the original
作为周期趋于无穷大的周期信号变为原来的
a periodic one that we have before and a 40 a series
周期性的事，我们面前和40系列
representation then becomes what we refer to as the Fourier transform so
表示就变成了我们所说的傅立叶变换，
that's just a quick look at kind of the basic idea
这只是一个快速浏览一下那种基本思路
and approach that will take in the next lecture will develop this
和方法，将在下一讲将开发这个
a little more carefully more fully moving from the 40 a series which we've
多一点小心地从40系列，我们已经更充分地移动
used for periodic signals
用于周期信号
to develop the for EA transform
以发展为EA变换
which will then be representation for a periodic see
这样会成为一个周期性见示意图
thank you
谢谢